[Ellis] Previously on Sterling Point…
I found, like, paperwork
in my dad's office today.
Gordon made my dad Ramona's guardian
before he died.
So is it kinda sounding like
your dad might also be Ramona's dad?
[Goldie] Joe, I hope
you still like mixtapes.
The baby just kicked.
I hate birthdays.
They make me feel closer to death.
You have a big one tomorrow.
You're gonna be 18, Annie.
Can I do something special for you?
Can I take you out tonight?
Hi. Hi. Hello.
Hi. This is my party.
I don't know anyone here.
-Hey.
-I got you something.
You did not have to do that.
That's so kind. I love it.
-It's Annie's birthday today.
-Oh.
-To Annie!
-Happy birthday.
-Thanks.
-Yeah, happy birthday! [whooping]
-Yeah!
-That's our girl!
-Yo, we are…
I'm sorry about what happened
with Stacey Mallory.
I did some stupid shit, I know that,
but please don't push me away.
You are the best thing in my life,
and I don't want to lose you or hurt you.
I don't know if--
[Rory] You wanna have sex?
-You've done it before, right?
-Yeah, so many times.
[soft music playing]
[Annie gasps softly]
Oh, my God.
[thuds]
[sighs]
Annie?
Dad.
-Are you… What?
-What are you…
-What are you doing here?
-Are you staying here?
-'Cause, you know, Denise said--
-No, I'm… I'm not.
-I'm just leaving, actually.
-Oh.
Oh, hey. Thank you so much.
I'll take 'em. Um…
Do you take American cash?
I don't have any Canadian.
No, Dad, this is… This is Ellis.
He's my friend.
Oh, yeah.
We met on the plane.
I didn't realize you guys
were already friends.
Look, can we go inside
so we can, you know, talk?
I have to… No, I'm gonna go home.
No, you haven't answered a single
one of my calls. What's going on?
I'll tell you later.
-When?
-Later.
-When later?
-[Annie] Later. It's all good.
[Steven] Hey! Annie.
-No, it's fine!
-Hey.
Is there any way I can get a ride?
Okay.
Annie, what time?
Dinner. Dinner-ish time.
-Can you… Be careful.
-[engine starts]
Just go, please, as fast as you can.
Ellis, I…
Oh, my God. Oh, my… Please look away.
Please look away. I'm so…
[Ramona gasps, screams]
[Ramona] Jesus Christ!
-Oh, my God.
-Help.
[Ramona] Yikes.
Too much fun?
-Too many shots.
-Right. Okay.
Alcohol is just poison. Did you know that?
Yeah, that is what they say.
Is it wrong to only believe in God
when you need him?
[Ramona] My God. Here, drink this.
You'll feel better.
Drink it slowly, though,
so you don't barf.
[Annie] Already did.
Hey, is that a… Is that a hungover tear?
Or a "something else is wrong" tear?
Um…
[sighs]
I'm just a whore. So…
[chuckles] What?
Mmm-hmm.
Yeah. I drank way too much.
-Right.
-Then I chain-smoked cigarettes.
-Wow. Okay.
-And then I…
went home with Rory.
-Oh, my God.
-Uh-huh. And we did stuff.
-Like, stuff-stuff.
-Wow.
I told him I'd done stuff before.
Just stop saying "stuff."
Did you guys fuck or not?
You had sex with Rory? That's just…
-Shh!
-Sorry. It's just so unexpected.
I know. I feel like I just, like,
lost my brain.
Like, misplaced my brain.
Like, did you not wanna do it?
No, I did want to.
I, like, really, really wanted to.
Okay. That's good.
No, now I feel anxious about it.
It's cool. Chill.
That's what's weird.
Like, I've never wanted to do something
in the moment and then done it.
And now I'm like,
does this mess up the Ellis thing?
Is there an Ellis situation?
I mean,
I feel like there's, like, a vibe, but…
-Okay.
-There won't be anymore,
after he saw me leaving Rory's.
-See, yeah, that's--
-Guess what else. Guess what else.
My dad was also there.
-Why was your dad there? What?
-To…
like, ruin my life, probably?
-Okay.
-To shame me for losing my virginity,
-on a whim.
-Yeah, you're fine.
I can't believe I lost my virginity
on a whim.
No, it's like, who am I? Like, I…
I'm scared of what I might do next.
What if I rob a bank?
What if I start a YouTube channel?
What if I become a singer?
[shushes] Drink some water. Okay?
It's… This is good.
Like, it's good to be messy sometimes.
It's important.
Like, way more important than whatever
you were made to think is important,
like, uh…
Like math.
-You know?
-No, that's actually really important.
Yeah. Yeah. Totally. I just…
Dude, look at how much you've,
like, grown and changed and evolved.
The beginning of the summer,
you were lying to yourself
about your obviously very gay boyfriend,
and now you're a whore.
-[chuckles] Kinda sick.
-[chuckles]
Yeah, no, you don't have
anything to feel guilty about.
Like, at all.
You were living in the moment.
It's what you wanted to do. And, yeah.
It's not what you planned,
but life's gonna happen
the way it happens.
-[chuckles] What?
-Okay. Who is this wise,
dare I say happy, Ramona?
What happened last night?
Mmm…
I guess, like,
Oona and I kind of happened.
[gasps] Did we lose our virginities
on the same night?
No, no. I… I'm classy, and I didn't
sleep with her on the first night.
I'm never telling you
-anything ever again.
-It's okay. It's okay.
Wait, I'm just… I'm curious.
Like, did it… Did it hurt?
Like, did you use a condom?
How did you even know what to do?
I'm serious.
Kind of.
Yes.
And I don't know.
["Running/Planning" playing]
Can I tell you something? Embarrassing?
Is it that you can't tell the difference
between blue and yellow socks?
Um, it's actually red and green.
And I know you think
my color blindness is hot.
Yeah. I do.
I really do. Very hot.
-Yeah? [chuckles]
-I actually think it's fascinating.
No, it's… It's something else.
I mean, yeah, tell me,
but you never have to feel embarrassed
about anything with me.
It's… It's so stupid, actually.
[Oona] I'm sure it's not.
I have this, like, weird insecurity about…
them.
These.
Why?
No, I mean, they are perfect.
You've never seen them.
Yeah, I don't need to see them
to know that.
It's kind of a thing for me.
That I don't really…
I don't like looking at them myself, even.
You down to tell me,
like, what it is about them
that's embarrassing?
Anything you say will not freak me out.
-[whispering indistinctly]
-Okay, what?
-[chuckles nervously]
-No. What? Who cares?
-I care. It's weird.
-That is not even bad, Ramona.
-It's weird.
-No, it's not.
There's nothing weird about that.
Oh, my God.
You are so beautiful.
Everything about you is beautiful.
That's sweet.
But you never have to show me
if you don't want to.
I'll still find you so attractive.
Do you say that to all the girls?
I don't know any other girls.
["On My Mind" playing]
[sighs]
[Rory] Are you also hungover? [laughs]
-Hey.
-Oh, man.
-It's like that?
-Oh.
-Have a little… No, it's okay, it's okay.
-Shit, I'm sorry.
Um…
Sorry, has my dad been weird?
Uh, he's mostly been on the balcony.
Like, staring into space.
That's actually pretty normal for him.
-Right.
-No worries.
Nonverbal dads. I've heard mine talk
eight times my whole life.
-It's an epidemic. We gotta help them.
-Right.
Thanks for letting us
have our weird dinner here.
-Family dinner, whatever it is.
-No, please.
You guys fit right in.
What?
You didn't say goodbye this morning.
Oh, sorry. I…
I just… I didn't wanna wake you up.
Always wake me up.
Yeah?
Okay. I'm gonna go rag on my mom
to give you guys some privacy,
because she can't read a room
to save her life.
-Okay.
-Come on. [exclaims awkwardly]
Mmm.
It's delicious.
Spaghetti is gas.
[Steven clears throat]
[clears throat]
You okay? You okay?
-No, got something in my throat.
-Just have some water.
Yeah.
Look, I'm…
I'm just not sure where to start.
You can start by apologizing.
Especially for not letting us know
that we owned a $22.7 million island.
-Connor, it's not the time for that.
-We can discuss that later.
Why do you always take her side?
I mean, she's the one who came here
and blew up everyone's lives.
Why don't you send her
to her room for once?
[Steven] I'm not. Connor. Please.
I need some air.
You're leaving?
Yeah, he has to go vape.
[Connor] Yeah, I… I can hear you.
[sighs]
Okay. Well…
[door closes]
I mean, I just hope you can understand now
that I couldn't tell you
about Ramona without, you know,
telling you about your mom's affair.
I didn't want you growing up
thinking about her that way,
and it was already hard enough
with her gone, you know?
What happened, Dad?
We were trying to get pregnant
for almost six years, and, you know,
-we did IVF…
-[door closes]
…and after the last round failed, we…
we were struggling.
And, um…
we got separated.
It was temporary.
But then we got the call about you guys.
Coming. You guys were everything
we'd ever dreamed of, so, you know,
we'd try and make it work, all together.
But your mom didn't wanna
live in New York anymore.
And she didn't want to do finance,
and she didn't want the life we had built,
so I… I tried to give her
as much space to figure out
why she was so unhappy.
I don't know why she was so unhappy.
But, um…
she had changed, that's what I know,
you know?
And her changing was bad?
I didn't say that. I…
She just wanted to live here,
and I said no.
Okay. Well, why didn't you guys
just get split custody or something?
Everything was on the table.
But…
then she told me she's pregnant.
So you filed for divorce
because of the affair?
No, she filed for divorce and refused
to bring you guys back home.
I had to get a lawyer and come here
and take you guys home with me.
Did you take us away from her?
-No!
-Did you take us away from her?
I took you to the place
that we agreed to raise you.
Which was our home in New York.
She was trying to keep you guys
away from me.
Did you know the affair was with Joe?
And that Ramona was his?
-Who told you that?
-That guy… Joe from the marina?
Ellis and I just found out,
but you cannot tell Ramona
under any circumstances,
because she's happy,
I can't drop another bomb on her.
If you and Ellis get together,
that would be incest, right?
Excuse me?
-Holy fuck. Shut up.
-Because if Joe is Ramona's dad,
-Not sure how the world works…
-Ellis is Joe's kid?
…but I think it's incest.
Annie, you can't do that.
You cannot hang out with that kid.
That is such a wild thing to say.
I'm try…
-Is it?
-Can you not hear yourself?
-Do you not hear it?
-What do you expect me to say after
-what happened to your mom?
-What did happen?
Because it sounds to me
like she was unhappy in her marriage
and in her life and in her job,
and so she came here
to try to make things better,
and I don't understand
why that's an insane thing to do.
'Cause she came up here and lost her mind!
That's what happened.
Okay.
Well, thank you for coming to apologize.
That was a stunning performance.
[Oona] Oof!
Babe, are you still hungover?
Babe, I honestly might be.
How did it go with your dad?
Um… Like, horrifically.
-No.
-Yeah.
-No. I'm sorry.
-That's okay. Not a big deal.
Thanks.
Yeah, it's just, like…
so heavy, I literally don't know
what to do with myself.
You should just, like,
tell him to fuck off and get outta here.
-[chuckles] Yeah. Yeah.
-Get out.
-I would love to do that.
-Do it.
-Can you do it for me?
-I feel like you should do it.
'Cause realistically,
we know I'm not gonna.
Hey, if you wanna avoid him,
come with us to Maple's show on Friday.
It's a real good time. It's fun.
We all crash and stay over,
'cause it's the last session.
All the kids are gone. It's a real party.
I just think I'm a little too dark
to do anything right now.
But thank you.
Fair, but is there any better cure
for darkness than the opportunity
to watch talentless children perform?
It's gonna make you feel better.
How talentless?
["We Got That Beat" playing]
-Is this your card?
-Um…
-No.
-[sighs]
Is this your card?
No.
-Oh, my God, I can't take it.
-[Ramona] I know. The little hat.
Is this your card?
Um…
no.
[whispers] Why are the cards so big?
[all whooping]
[Annie] Go, Maple!
-[Oona] Yes, Maple!
-[Ellis] Yeah!
[vehicles starting]
[laughing]
-Bye, Maple.
-Bye, Maple!
-See you next year.
-Bye!
[Sully] Maple, my baby!
That performance altered
my brain chemistry
in a way that needs to be studied,
thank you.
You sent in the clowns.
-The clowns were sent hard, mama, yeah.
-You did.
-So good. I'm so proud of you.
-It was beautiful.
-Did you remember?
-Yeah. I did.
-Voilà.
-Long-form journalism!
Can you give us the rundown
on what happened this week?
Don't miss a detail. I wanna hear it all.
Um, I got, like,
a lot better at improv.
-Yes, and…
-Okay.
[Maple] I tried archery.
That was not for me.
Played capture-the-flag, got my period.
-Then I beaded this cool bracelet--
-[Oona] Wait, what?
-You got your period?
-Oh, my God, cong-- Did--
-Congratulations.
-Welcome to hell.
Yay, period.
Please stop. Like, everyone stop do--
I can't believe I wasn't there for it.
This is huge.
This is big. Let's commemorate it.
I'll make you a period crown.
-[Maple] What?
-A period crown.
Please, no.
Um, okay. I need cinnamon bark,
I need red peony root.
-[Sully] There she goes.
-I don't think there's any stopping this.
[Ramona] No, sorry.
Be careful of the poison ivy.
Wait. I'm sorry.
Did you just say you had perfect pitch?
-[Sully] Oh!
-[both humming]
-Okay, so…
-It's really cool.
…the ancient ancestors
would bleed straight into the earth
-as a gift.
-Whose ancestors?
-Wait, that's so cool.
-[Oona] Yeah, really cool.
And then the first blood,
it gets buried straight into the earth,
and a tree gets planted on top.
Well, my first blood
is all over my flannel pajama pants, so…
Maple, please, this is, like,
an important moment in your life.
It's just not a big deal. Like…
I mean, it's also, like,
not not a big deal.
Right? Like,
it's exciting to have a ceremony.
It's cool you have a sister
that would do that for you.
I didn't even… I didn't even tell anyone.
-Why not?
-Because I didn't have a…
-sister or a mom to tell.
-[Oona] Mmm.
That sounded way sadder
than how I meant it. Sorry.
No, I mean, you're telling us now, so…
True. Guys, I got my period.
-[Oona] You did.
-[Ramona] Hell, yeah.
-Breaking news.
-I made you a tincture for your cramps.
I don't have any cramps.
[Oona] Okay, yeah. Just wait.
The first one, it's deceptively easy,
and then they get…
they get a little worse, and…
Yeah, no. Mine are diabolical.
A murder scene in the toilet.
-[Ramona] It's fine, but gets worse.
-There are clots.
-[Oona] Clots.
-Yeah.
-Sickly satisfying though.
-A little man jackhammering
-your stomach, like "Ta-ta-ta…"
-Yeah. Scaffolding on the uterus.
Fetal position on the bathroom floor.
I'm gonna swim home now, guys.
No, no, no, no, no.
Hey, it's okay. It's not that bad.
-It… Well…
-It is… Uh…
I'll be there for you.
Okay, I've got an idea.
On the count of three,
can we please all howl towards Jupiter?
-I refuse to howl.
-[Ramona] Good idea.
-Come on.
-Let's do it.
-Yeah.
Yeah, let's go. Ready?
Just… One, two, three.
[both howling]
Come on, come on.
Do this for Oona.
-Throw her a bone.
-Come on.
-Okay, ready?
-Okay.
[all howling]
-Queen Maple.
-All hail our period queen Maple.
-All hail. Our period queen.
-Come on, come on.
-No, stay, stay, stay, stay, stay.
-Periods, periods, periods…
-Periods, periods, periods,
-periods, periods, periods, periods.
-…periods, periods, periods, periods.
Maybe this is the benefit
of having your period.
You can get carried around
for the rest of your life every month.
-Yeah.
-Not really worth it. Oh!
Oh!
Hey.
-Hey.
Um, sorry if you guys
were sleeping in here,
I can go somewhere else, it's--
It's fine.
There's ten bunk beds in here.
Please don't make it weird, guys.
[Annie chuckles] Okay.
-She planned this.
-Yeah. Yeah, she did.
I can, like, actually
totally sleep on the beach. It's--
Sleep in sand?
-Yes.
-[chuckles] That's crazy.
-What?
-You should just sleep in here.
-Okay.
-In a bed. It is fine with me.
-Cool.
-Hardcore of you, though. That's cool.
-I'd feel comfortable.
-Sick.
-[Annie laughs]
Thanks.
What do you…
What do you think, uh,
we should do about Ramona?
It's been on my mind all day.
Yeah. Um…
I left the tape out for my dad.
But he hasn't said anything.
Yeah? Sorry.
I've been feeling really bad. Just, like--
What? No. No, no, no, don't.
Don't. He should be the one
to talk to Ramona.
I mean, he's the adult. Like…
Or allegedly. [scoffs]
Yeah.
[sighs]
Is your dad trying to make you leave?
Yeah.
I'm sorry for what happened the other day.
I was caught off guard, and…
-All good.
-I…
Yeah.
I'm not, like, dating Rory.
-Okay.
-I'm not… Not that I'm assuming
that you would care if I was, I just…
And…
-Gotcha.
-Not…
Do you care?
Don't answer that. Sorry I asked you that.
Sorry I asked you that.
You're… You're fine.
Ellis, I'm sorry. Sometimes I literally
cannot tell if you hate me.
What? Why? What are you--
Yeah, I'm sorry. I…
It's fine if you do. I…
-[chuckles]
-I just…
-What?
-Annie, I…
Do you? [chuckles nervously]
I actually can't even think of one thing
I don't like about you.
Really?
Yeah.
-Should we go inside?
-Yeah.
-Yeah, we…
-Cool. It's getting cold.
Yeah. Yeah.
-Cool.
-We should.
A little bit.
-Long night, huh?
-Yeah.
-How good was Maple?
-Oh, she was amazing.
Yeah.
-It was insane. She was so good.
-Yeah.
So cute.
-Oh, my God.
-Oops.
Annie, it's me.
Hello?
[slow music playing]
We're closed.
Yeah, not here for that.
[Joe] What are you doing here?
Getting my kids out of here
as quickly as possible.
So, nothing's changed.
What'd you just say?
I'm pretty sure you heard me.
I heard you're not taking care of Ramona.
Who the fuck do you think you are?
You ruined how many lives
to not even raise her?
How do you live with yourself, man?
What story are you telling?
You know, the only one
telling the story here is you, pal.
Okay.
Well, you can tell your kid
it's not gonna work out with Annie.
-Excuse me?
-Yeah, that's what I said.
She won't make
the same mistakes Goldie made.
You know exactly what happened to Goldie
and it sure as hell wasn't me.
Yeah, you were a distraction.
This whole place is a distraction.
It was the biggest mistake of her life.
Or was that going to New York
to be with you?
-Because she came back here.
-Yeah, she wasn't thinking rationally.
You were thinking rationally
when you took her kids from her?
She took them from me.
You showed up in the middle of the night
with a goddamn lawyer, Steven.
You think I wanted that?
The fact that what happened to her
doesn't eat you up inside
-every single day of your life…
-What the fuck do you know, man?
Well, I know she didn't love you anymore.
I know that she wasn't sure she ever did.
[grunts]
Fuck!
Goddamn it, man!
Argh!
See, that's what happens
when you don't think
you're as weak as you really are.
Fuck!
You were so sweet with Maple today.
No. She hated it.
No, she didn't.
I just didn't want her to feel
like our mum wasn't there, you know?
Mmm.
You were perfect, though. Really.
I wish Annie and I would've had that.
You will.
You have your whole future with her.
She's not gonna go anywhere.
Yeah.
And I am not gonna go anywhere either.
-So you better get used to it.
-[chuckles]
Okay.
I'm not going anywhere either.
-Really?
-No.
So you better deal with that.
Okay.
You're so beautiful.
Annie?
Mmm-hmm?
I feel like my childhood is over.
It's not.
I promise it's not.
Does it get easier?
Your period? 'Cause I still bleed
-through my pants all the time.
-No! No, like, growing up.
[Annie laughs] Oh. Um…
I'm gonna be super real with you.
No.
[Maple] Oh.
[chuckles] No, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I should not have said that. Uh…
No, this is where me not having a mom
becomes scarily obvious.
I understand why you're scared.
It's like, growing up and changing,
and getting old, and,
like, feeling out of control,
it's really, like…
It's really freaky.
And please don't vomit as I say this,
but it's also kinda…
a new chapter, right?
Which is pretty exciting.
What I feel right now is just,
like, weird.
I get that.
But it won't feel that way forever.
[Maple] So, when does childhood end?
[sighs]
I guess… I guess, like, maybe
when you stop worrying that it's over?
I'll be right back, okay?
-Hey.
-[Ellis] Hey.
You okay?
Yeah.
I just don't remember getting my period.
Right.
[Annie] Yeah.
Like, it just occurred to me
how sad that is.
I don't really remember that moment.
Like…
Like, I guess I went to the bodega alone
and, like, bought tampons.
And, like, looked up on YouTube
how to put one in?
Like, it's kinda sad.
I don't really think I had, like…
like, experienced my childhood.
And there's nothing anyone can do
to make me feel better about it,
that it's over, because it's over
and I will never get it back.
And I'm so mad at my dad for that.
I think.
Like, like,
why was it my responsibility to, like,
make my childhood a childhood?
Like, I feel like he took…
I took the fall for him or something.
You know?
I took the fall for him.
Like, I guess I couldn't be a kid,
so that he could be sad?
Like, why did he let me do that?
Okay, do you know what I did
on my birthday every year?
This is really funny.
I would go to the doctor
for my annual exam.
'Cause I thought that that's what
you were supposed to do on your birthday.
Who let me do that?
And I would schedule it myself.
No fucking wonder I hate birthdays.
[groaning]
Like, I wish this was a closet.
I would… As a kid, I would, like,
go into my closet…
It was just, like, comforting. Um…
But is that weird to do as an adult?
To, like, sit in a closet?
I guess I have, like, taxes to file.
Like…
I know everyone probably feels this way,
but I just wish I could go back
and do it differently.
Because then I probably
wouldn't be like this.
And then I could just, like, be fixed.
Oh, my God. I can't believe
I just said all that to you.
Annie, you don't…
You don't need to be fixed, though.
Seriously.
Feeling hardcore enough to…
sleep on the beach?
Okay.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
-Thank you.
-Be gentle.
Want me to call my lawyer? He's a shark.
No, I'm fine. It's okay.
[sighs]
But if you can tell my kids
they're not Canadian
and convince them to come home
with me, that'd be nice.
Just explain how socialist taxes work.
They'll be running back to New York.
-Yeah, that's for sure.
-Right?
You're gonna be okay.
Promise.
Yeah.
[Steven sighs]
She's been dead a long time, honey.
You gotta bury her.
[sighs]
Could you tell me a story?
So I can ignore my impending doom
and try to fall asleep?
Okay. Uh…
I could…
I could tell you how to, like,
build a canoe.
If that's cool with you.
-That is perfect.
-That's all I got.
[both chuckle]
-That's exactly what I need.
-Okay.
-I've always wondered how.
-Okay, good.
[clears throat]
-All right.
-Okay.
So, um…
I guess you start with, like,
finding the right cuts of pine, right?
And then you have to, like,
use, like, this special tool
to, like, shape them and curve the wood,
but you can't snap it.
So it does take some time.
You have to be patient with it.
And, like, a canoe isn't
just, like, carved…
[Joe] Where'd you find that?
Ellis left it out.
I'm assuming for you?
Okay, yeah.
Why didn't you say something?
That's the first thing you're gonna say?
Are you serious?
Were you going to leave?
I didn't leave.
That wasn't my question.
[sighs] Were you in love with her?
Oh, come on. This… [sighs]
We're talking about something
that was almost 20 years ago.
-I was young, I was confused.
-And this all happened while I was away?
With our baby?
Just taking care of my sick mother alone.
-Kate, I--
-You what?
-This is the life that I wanted.
-[scoffs]
Oh, great.
I'm so glad you got what you wanted.
-That is not what I meant.
-[sighs]
Is Ramona yours?
-[sighs] Can we just--
-Joe.
[sighing]
Is she?
And you haven't told her.
Who are you?
[sniffles]
-Good morning.
-Hi.
Made you something.
You didn't.
-I did.
-You…
-Oh, I could cry right now.
-I know, but--
I will cry in private later.
-Thank you.
-This is… I can't believe you did this.
Yeah. Yeah.
Why does it look so good?
I did props on Midsommar.
Okay, we have a professional.
-Yeah, no.
-Thank you for this.
This is so cool.
Thanks.
Since I didn't get to make you one
when it actually happened.
God, I wish our kid selves
got to hang out.
-Yeah. I do, I do too.
-Right?
I wish we could've, like,
fought each other.
We'd be so mad at each other one second,
like, over something stupid,
and then not care a second later.
-Yeah. Rat each other out for stuff.
-I would never rat.
-Please.
-I would've been the worst tattletale.
Yeah.
This is gonna sound weird, but…
I feel like now that I know you,
I miss her more.
-[sighs] Yeah.
-Yeah.
Almost felt like I didn't have the right
to be sad about it
'cause I didn't have her to begin with.
So, I get that.
I sort of feel like I did have her.
Like, as a mom.
That she was real because I have you.
You know, like a sister.
[Annie chuckles softly]
I can't believe
you just called me your sister.
-Take it. Okay.
-I am. I love it.
Can you say it again?
-Okay, don't push it. Okay.
-Okay.
["Big Wheel" playing]
[inaudible]
[chattering indistinctly]
[Oona] Wait, wait, guys,
I've got the egg ick right now.
-[Sully] Egg ick?
-Ugh, I hate the egg ick.
I had that for, like, a year once.
It was horrible.
Hi.
Hey, Dad, what are you doing here?
-Um…
-Why do you have a black eye?
Oh, Joe kicked his ass.
-Like, real…
-[Steven] Okay. All right.
[Connor] Real Gen X
"when a punch is thrown" kinda thing.
Right? Isn't it weird?
She looks just like Mom.
Yo, what's up? I'm Ramona.
Nice to meet you.
Dead mom's twin.
Really appreciate you, you know,
keeping me and my siblings apart
for our whole lives. Really cool.
Okay. That's not… I'm sorry, but
-what hap-- I'm sorry.
-Yeah. Yeah.
-It's time to go.
-No, I'm not.
Yeah. Get your stuff, please.
I'm not leaving.
I'm the only family Ramona has.
Steven, honey, end this now.
-No, what?
-It's kinda getting cruel at this point.
Denise is right, Dad.
-Yeah. Yes.
-No. Guys, no.
-Tell Ramona and get on with your lives.
-Enough. Not now.
-Tell me what?
-[Steven] Don't say anything.
Joe is your dad, Ramona.
He is too afraid to tell you and Steven…
It's not fair to him anymore,
or, frankly, to you, honey,
and I'm so sorry
that you had to find out like this.
-There, I've said it. Now it's done.
-Jesus Christ, Denise.
You two knew?
Joe knows?
Say something.
Gordon made him your guardian
when he died.
-Ramona, I--
-Annie, you said…
You said, "No more secrets."
-No, I know--
-Ramona. Hey, Ramona, wait.
[Sully] Ramona.
["White Horses" playing]
Actually, fuck all of you.
Fuck you.
[Annie] Oona, I…
Wait!
Ramona!